<resources>
    <string-array name="questions">
        <item>Does Joy-Con Droid work on my phone?</item>
        <item>Can you make Joy-Con Droid work on my phone?</item>
        <item>Can Joy-Con Droid harm my Nintendo Switch?</item>
        <item>What should I do if Joy-Con Droid disconnects after leaving Change Grip/Order Screen?</item>
        <item>What should I do if Joy-Con Droid does not get Pairing Request?</item>
        <item>What should I do if there is input delay?</item>
        <item>Does Joy-Con Droid work with all Switch Firmware Versions?</item>
        <item>How can I get help or request feature/information?</item>
        <item>How can I add my own UI to the application?</item>
        <item>Why do you need my MAC address?</item>
        <item>How do I find my MAC address?</item>
        <item>How do change/remove MAC address or Never Ask Again decision?</item>
        <item>Can I join to testing program?</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="answers">
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            This application requires <b>Android 9 (P) or higher</b>. It uses HID profile which some
            manufacturers did not include in their <b>System Software</b>. You can check device
            compatibility through <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.rdapps.bluetoothhidtester">
            Bluetooth HID Profile Tester</a>.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            If your system software is missing HID profile; this only can be fixed with <b>System Update</b>
            which can be only provided by <b>Device Manufacturer</b>. If you definitely want to use this app
            you can install <a href="https://lineageos.org/">Lineage OS</a>.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            <b>Joy-Con Droid</b> is used already by many users and so far did not cause any irreversible errors.
            Occasionally, Nintendo Switch might crash but resetting the console fixes this problem.
            However, use <b>Joy-Con Droid</b> application at your own risk. <b>Joy-Con Droid</b> does
            not come with any guarantees.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            "Continuous disconnecting when Change Order/Grip screen is left." is a known issue however
            there is no known fix for this problem yet. However, there is a workaround:
            <ol>
                <li>Go to Change Order/Grip Screen.</li>
                <li>Wait for Bluetooth Pairing Request but <b>DO NOT ACCEPT!</b></li>
                <li>Go one step back to controller menu.</li>
                <li>Now accept pairing request.</li>
                <li>Connection should be established.</li>
            </ol>
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            If <b>Joy-Con Droid</b> does not get pairing request even though you are on <b>Change Order
            /Grip</b> screen. There is couple of check you need to do. Check if your device has desired
            device name for bluetooth such as Joy-Con (R), Joy-Con (L), or Pro Controller.
            If device name is correctly set. Close the application and click notification to kill the
            service. Go to settings and choose disconnect controllers option on you Nintendo Switch.
            Turn off the bluetooth. (You might wanna restart your Android Device). Once all these steps
            are completed. Open the <b>Change Order/Grip</b> screen and open <b>Joy-Con Droid</b> and
            repeat connection steps.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            Another known issue is input delay, reconnecting usually fix the input delay issue.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            <b>Joy-Con Droid</b> tested up to Nintendo Switch Version <b>9.0.0</b>. There is no guarantee
            <b>Joy-Con Droid</b> will continue you to work on higher versions of Nintendo Switch firmware.
            Please check <b>Joy-Con Droid</b> to see latest supported version before updating your Nintendo Switch Version
            firmware.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            There are couple of ways you can reach to the developer:
            <ul>
                <li><a href="mailto:allplaylive@gmail.com">Email</a></li>
                <li><a href="https://youtubeplays.com/joycon-droid">Discord</a></li>
            </ul>
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            You can check the example project <a href="https://github.com/YouTubePlays/JoyConDroidNESStyleController">NES Style Controller</a>.
            If wanna develop a similar UI or any useful script contact to the developer.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            <b>Joy-Con and Pro Controller</b> sends their MAC address to <b>Nintendo Switch</b>. This information is used to reconnect. However,
            in <b>Android OS</b> it is not possible to access a devices MAC address. User may choose to provide MAC address inorder to
            improve connection quality.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            In most devices following steps would be sufficient to find Bluetooth MAC address:
            <ol>
                <li>From the <b>Home</b> screen, open the app drawer, then open <b>“Settings“</b>.</li>
                <li>Select <b>“System“</b>. (Skip this step on some models)</li>
                <li>Scroll down to the bottom and tap <b>“About Phone“, “About device“, or “About tablet“</b>.</li>
                <li>Scroll down to the bottom and tap <b>“Status“</b>.</li>
                <li>Scroll down and the <b>“Bluetooth address”</b> will be shown in the list.</li>
            </ol>
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            If you want to remove or change MAC address entered or simply change Never Ask Again Decision:
            Open the side menu from top left menu icon and tap <b>Revert Bluetooth Configuration</b>.
            ]]>
        </item>
        <item>
            <![CDATA[
            If you do want to see the latest state of the <b>Joy-Con Droid</b>, you can join the tester group.
            However, be aware testing group might have more problems time to time and updated frequently.
            <a href="mailto:allplaylive@gmail.com">Email</a> or join to <a href="https://youtubeplays.com/joycon-droid">Discord</a>
            for more information.
            ]]>
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
